Guide to the Thomas Raynesford Lounsbury Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, Series I
  - Raymond, Mrs. James, 1895 (Box 18, Folder 376)
  - Redmond, W. A., 1906 (Box 18, Folder 377)
  - Reed, Edward Bliss, 1897-1909 (Box 18, Folder 377)
  - Reed, Elizabeth (Mrs. Edward), 1911 (Box 18, Folder 377)
  - Reid, J. R., 1884 (Box 18, Folder 377)
  - Reid, Whitelaw, 1872-1884 (Box 18, Folder 377)
  - Reiley, A. C., 1894-1895 (Box 18, Folder 377)
  - Relling, James, 1883 (Box 18, Folder 377)
  - Reyer, T. E., 1884 (Box 18, Folder 377)
  - Rhodes, James Ford, 1903-1913 (Box 18, Folder 378)
  - Ricaud, A. C., 1884 (Box 18, Folder 378)
  - Rice, Charles Elmer, 1912 (Box 18, Folder 378)
  - Rice, John, 1889 (Box 18, Folder 378)
  - Rice, Wallace, 1912 (Box 18, Folder 378)
  - Rich, S. M., 1907 (Box 18, Folder 379)
  - Richards, Agnes E., 1895 (Box 18, Folder 379)
  - Richards, Alfred E., 1905 (Box 18, Folder 379)
  - Richards, Charles B., 1896 (Box 18, Folder 379)
  - Richards, Eugene Lamb, 1893 (Box 18, Folder 379)
  - Richardson, Charles A., 1893-1897 (Box 18, Folder 380)
  - Richardson, Charles Francis, 1879-1897 (Box 18, Folder 380)
  - Richardson, M. L., 1902 (Box 18, Folder 380)
  - Richmond, George H., 1878-1889 (Box 18, Folder 380)
  - Richmond, Harold A., 1889 (Box 18, Folder 380)
  - Riddell, Herbert, 1914 (Box 18, Folder 381)
  - Rideing, William Henry, 1913 (Box 18, Folder 381)
  - Rider, Sidney, 1882 (Box 18, Folder 381)
  - Ridgway, Eliza L., 1895 (Box 18, Folder 381)
  - Rinehart, Walter H., 1907 (Box 18, Folder 381)
  - Ring, Henry Wilson, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 381)
  - Ripley, Dwight, 1892 (Box 18, Folder 382)
  - Ripley, George, 1865 (Box 18, Folder 382)
  - Risley, Florence, 1909 (Box 18, Folder 382)
  - Robbins, Edward D., 1893 (Box 18, Folder 382)
  - Robbins, Richard W., 1910 (Box 18, Folder 382)
  - Roberts, Ellis Henry, 1896 (Box 18, Folder 383)
  - Roberts, M. A., 1872 (Box 18, Folder 383)
  - Roberts, Margaret, 1902-1906 (Box 18, Folder 383)
  - Robins, Sally Nelson, 1910 (Box 18, Folder 383)
  - Robinson, George W., 1913 (Box 18, Folder 384)
  - Robinson, Luther E., 1904 (Box 18, Folder 384)
  - Robinson, Sarah A. K., 1896 (Box 18, Folder 384)
  - Robinson, Tracy Margaret, 1911 (Box 18, Folder 384)
  - Robinson, William Clarke, 1891-1896 (Box 18, Folder 384)
  - Rodgers, James F., 1884 (Box 18, Folder 385)
  - Roedell, Gustav A., 1892 (Box 18, Folder 385)
  - Rogers, Faith Helen, 1911 (Box 18, Folder 385)
  - Rogers, Henry Wade, 1907 (Box 18, Folder 385)
  - Rogers, Howard J., 1904-1905 (Box 18, Folder 385)
  - Rogers, Ralph, 1913 (Box 18, Folder 385)
  - Rolfe, William J., 1871-1909 (Box 18, Folder 386)
  - Rollins, Mabel, 1912 (Box 18, Folder 386)
  - Romeike, Albert, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 386)
  - Rood, Henry E.(*), 1903-1913 (Box 18, Folder 387)
  - Rood, Robert B., 1881-1883 (Box 18, Folder 388)
  - Roorbach, Harold, 1882 (Box 18, Folder 388)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore(*), 1888-1912 (Box 18, Folder 389)
  - Root, G. L., 1882 (Box 18, Folder 390)
  - Royce, Charles S., 1882 (Box 18, Folder 390)
  - Ruben, Edward, 1884 (Box 18, Folder 390)
  - Rumsey, Olive, undated (Box 18, Folder 390)
  - Runkle, Lucia G.(*), 1880-1903 (Box 18, Folder 391)
  - Rusby, Henry Hurd, 1874-1876 (Box 18, Folder 392)
  - Russell, H., 1906 (Box 18, Folder 392)
  - Russell, John A., 1888 (Box 18, Folder 392)
  - Russell, S. M., 1906 (Box 18, Folder 392)
  - Russell, Talcott H., 1889-1909 (Box 18, Folder 392)
  - Ryerson, John A., 1907 (Box 18, Folder 392)
  - Ryman, Thaddeus B., 1896 (Box 18, Folder 392)
  - S - General (Box 18, Folder 393)
  - Sabin, Frances E., 1913 (Box 18, Folder 394)
  - Sadler, Sophie, 1909 (Box 18, Folder 394)
  - Sage, Dean, 1883-1897 (Box 18, Folder 394)
  - Sage, Sarah (Mrs. Dean), 1893 (Box 18, Folder 394)
  - Saintsbury, George, 1889-1902 (Box 18, Folder 394)
  - Salisbury, E. E., 1896 (Box 18, Folder 394)
  - Sallmon, William H., 1896 (Box 18, Folder 394)
  - Salter, Charles C., 1892 (Box 18, Folder 394)
  - Samson, D. W., 1889 (Box 18, Folder 395)
  - Sanborn, Franklin B., 1900-1904 (Box 18, Folder 395)
  - Sanders, Frank K., 1900 (Box 18, Folder 395)
  - Sanders, Walter Murray, 1883-1903 (Box 18, Folder 395)
  - Sanderson, Robert Louis, 1907 (Box 18, Folder 395)
  - [Sandford?], undated (Box 18, Folder 395)
  - Sanford, E. H., 1882 (Box 18, Folder 395)
  - Sargent, Edward R., 1913 (Box 18, Folder 396)
  - Sargent, Henry B., 1887 (Box 18, Folder 396)
  - Sargent, Helen White(*), 1912-1915 (Box 18, Folder 396)
  - Sargent, Homer Earle, 1886 (Box 18, Folder 397)
  - Sargent, Joseph B., 1886 (Box 18, Folder 397)
  - Sargent, Laura, undated (Box 18, Folder 397)
  - Saunders, Frederick, 1882 (Box 18, Folder 397)
  - Savage, Richard Henry(*), 1892-1894 (Box 19, Folder 398)
  - Savidge, William, 1894 (Box 19, Folder 398)
  - Sawtelle, Alice E., 1894 (Box 19, Folder 398)
  - Schauffler, Robert Haven, 1911 (Box 19, Folder 399)
  - Schelling, Felix, 1913 (Box 19, Folder 399)
  - Schelling, T., 1909 (Box 19, Folder 399)
  - Scherill, Julius, 1898 (Box 19, Folder 399)
  - Schevill, Rudolf, 1907 (Box 19, Folder 399)
  - Schipp, Florence L., 1911 (Box 19, Folder 399)
  - Schmidt, L. W., 1875-1877 (Box 19, Folder 399)
  - Schobinger, John J., 1892 (Box 19, Folder 400)
  - Schofield, Henry, 1905-1911 (Box 19, Folder 400)
  - Schumaker, Charles A., 1894 (Box 19, Folder 400)
  - Schwab, John Christopher, 1905-1912 (Box 19, Folder 400)
  - Schwartz, L. A., 1885 (Box 19, Folder 400)
  - Scott, Charles P. G.(*), 1882-1914 (Box 19, Folder 401-402)
  - Scott, Edmund D., 1893 (Box 19, Folder 403)
  - Scott, Frank Hall, 1898 (Box 19, Folder 403)
  - Scott, John C., 1895-1912 (Box 19, Folder 403)
  - Scott, Lillian A., 1906-1907, undated (Box 19, Folder 403)
  - Scott, Mary Augusta(*), 1893-1905 (Box 19, Folder 404-405)
  - Scott, Winfield, 1882-1904 (Box 19, Folder 406)
  - Scribner, Arthur Hawley, 1901 (Box 19, Folder 406)
  - Scribner, Charles, 1883 (Box 19, Folder 406)
  - Scribner's(*), 1878-1911 (Box 19, Folder 407)
    See: William Crary Brownell, box 2, folder 54 See: Edward L. Burlingame, box 3, folder 62
  - Scudder, Horace Elisha, 1899 (Box 19, Folder 408)
  - Scudder, Sylvia C., 1901 (Box 19, Folder 408)
  - Sebring, A. J., 1884-1905 (Box 19, Folder 408)
  - Sechter, E. T., 1905 (Box 19, Folder 408)
  - Sedgwick, G. Stanley, undated (Box 19, Folder 408)
  - Sedgwick, Henry Dwight, 1913-1914 (Box 19, Folder 408)
  - Sedgwick, Mary Douglas, 1902 (Box 19, Folder 408)
  - Sedgwick, S. M., 1913 (Box 19, Folder 408)
  - Sedgwick, William T.(*), 1904-1905 (Box 19, Folder 409)
  - Seelye, L. Clarke, 1884-1887 (Box 19, Folder 409)
  - Seerley, Homer H., 1910 (Box 19, Folder 410)
  - Seligman, Edwin R. A., 1913 (Box 19, Folder 410)
  - Sellers, Alfred L., 1878 (Box 19, Folder 410)
  - Severy, Ernest E., 1894-1915 (Box 19, Folder 410)
  - Sexton, F. Maurice, 1911 (Box 19, Folder 410)
  - Seymour, George Dudley(*), 1895-1912 (Box 19, Folder 411)
  - Seymour, Thomas Day, 1887-1892 (Box 19, Folder 411)
  - Shafer, Robert E., 1910 (Box 19, Folder 412)
  - Shallier, Guy Wheeler, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 412)
  - Shannon, Leona Johnson, 1907 (Box 19, Folder 412)
  - Shattuck, Sidney Frank, 1901 (Box 19, Folder 412)
  - Shaw, E. C., 1894 (Box 19, Folder 412)
  - Shaw, Fanny (Mrs. H. C.), 1907 (Box 19, Folder 412)
  - Shaw, H. C., 1908 (Box 19, Folder 412)
  - Sheffield, George St. John, 1893-1913 (Box 19, Folder 413)
  - Sheffield, Joseph E., 1875-1881 (Box 19, Folder 413)
  - Shelden, Henry, 1913 (Box 19, Folder 413)
  - Sheldon, Charles, 1911 (Box 19, Folder 413)
  - Sheldon, Clarence Wellington, 1882 (Box 19, Folder 413)
  - Shelley Society
    See: James Mills Pierce, box 16, folder 354
  - Shelton, William A., 1880 (Box 19, Folder 413)
  - Shepard, Frederick J., 1906-1907 (Box 19, Folder 413)
  - Sheridan, Susan Smith, 1901 (Box 19, Folder 414)
  - Sherman, Gordon Edward, 1879 (Box 19, Folder 414)
  - Sherman, Lucius A.(*), 1874-1915 (Box 19, Folder 414)
  - Sherman, P. Tecumseh, 1908-1915 (Box 19, Folder 415)
  - Sherman, T. E., undated (Box 19, Folder 415)
  - Shideler, A. N., 1914 (Box 19, Folder 415)
  - Shill, Ephraim, 1909 (Box 19, Folder 415)
  - Shippen, Edward, 1883 (Box 19, Folder 415)
  - Shockley, William, 1914 (Box 19, Folder 415)
  - Shrere, Grace, 1908 (Box 19, Folder 415)
  - Siebke, E. H., 1891 (Box 19, Folder 415)
  - Sill, Edmund Rowland, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 416)
  - Simmons, Edward, 1906 (Box 20, Folder 416)
  - Simms, William Alexander, 1890 (Box 20, Folder 416)
  - Simms, William H., 1890 (Box 20, Folder 416)
  - Sims, H. F., 1913 (Box 20, Folder 416)
  - Sinclair, A. T., 1909 (Box 20, Folder 416)
  - Singer, Isidor, 1911 (Box 20, Folder 417)
  - Skeat, Walter William, 1892-1909 (Box 20, Folder 417)
  - Skeel, Rufus, 1900 (Box 20, Folder 417)
  - Skinner, Joseph, 1878 (Box 20, Folder 417)
  - Slade, A. J., 1890 (Box 20, Folder 417)
  - Sloan, Mary, 1905-1907 (Box 20, Folder 418)
  - Sloane, William M.(*), 1881-1914 (Box 20, Folder 418)
  - Smalley, George Washburn, 1892 (Box 20, Folder 418)
  - Smith, Benjamin Eli(*), 1886-1900 (Box 20, Folder 419)
  - Smith, C. Alphonso, 1913 (Box 20, Folder 420)
  - Smith, C. H., 1895 (Box 20, Folder 420)
  - Smith, Cora M., 1902 (Box 20, Folder 420)
  - Smith, Emily D., 1900 (Box 20, Folder 420)
  - Smith, Eugene, 1873-1902 (Box 20, Folder 420)
  - Smith, F. E., 1874 (Box 20, Folder 420)
  - Smith, F. W., Jr., 1912 (Box 20, Folder 420)
  - Smith, Francis Hopkinson(*), 1905-1914 (Box 20, Folder 421)
  - Smith, George Barnett, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 422)
  - Smith, Harry Dwight, 1895 (Box 20, Folder 422)
  - Smith, Hay Watson, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 422)
  - Smith, Herbert Augustine, 1891-1899 (Box 20, Folder 422)
  - Smith, James R., 1901 (Box 20, Folder 422)
  - Smith, Justin, 1892 (Box 20, Folder 422)
  - Smith, Lewis, 1875 (Box 20, Folder 422)
  - Smith, Lloyd Waddell, 1894 (Box 20, Folder 422)
  - Smith, Munroe, 1906-1908 (Box 20, Folder 422)
  - Smith, Q. P., 1900 (Box 20, Folder 423)
  - Smith, R. T., 1913 (Box 20, Folder 423)
  - Smith, Robert Atwater, 1907 (Box 20, Folder 423)
  - Smith, Sidney I., 1894-1895 (Box 20, Folder 423)
  - Smith, Stephen R., 1876-1880 (Box 20, Folder 423)
  - Smith, Virginia T., 1883 (Box 20, Folder 423)
  - Smith, W. S., 1908 (Box 20, Folder 423)
  - Smoke, Samuel A., 1906 (Box 20, Folder 424)
  - Smoke, Susie, 1904 (Box 20, Folder 424)
  - Smyth, Albert H.(*), 1884-1905 (Box 20, Folder 424)
  - Sneath, Elias H., 1905 (Box 20, Folder 424)
  - Snedeker, H. M., 1882 (Box 20, Folder 425)
  - Snelgrove, A. G., 1877-1879 (Box 20, Folder 425)
  - Snell, Ada L., 1906 (Box 20, Folder 425)
  - Snowden, Mrs. E. G., 1885 (Box 20, Folder 425)
  - Snyder, Zacharias X., 1913 (Box 20, Folder 425)
  - Sockwood, Sara E. (Mrs. William), 1887 (Box 20, Folder 425)
  - Solburg, Thorvald, 1888 (Box 20, Folder 425)
  - Southworth, H. W., 1883 (Box 20, Folder 425)
  - Sparrow, L. Edwards, 1890-1891 (Box 20, Folder 426)
  - Speer, Howard, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 426)
  - Speirs, Frederick W., 1901 (Box 20, Folder 426)
  - Spence, Gertrude, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 426)
  - Spencer, H. W., 1889 (Box 20, Folder 426)
  - Spencer, T. Henry, 1891 (Box 20, Folder 426)
  - Sperry, M. L., 1902 (Box 20, Folder 426)
  - Spicer, P., 1914 (Box 20, Folder 426)
  - Spingarn, Joel Elias, 1913 (Box 20, Folder 426)
  - Sprague, Albert C.(*), 1888-1907 (Box 20, Folder 427)
  - Sprague, Charles E., 1903 (Box 20, Folder 427)
  - Sprague, Nancy A., 1901 (Box 20, Folder 427)
  - Sprague, Otho S., 1895-1896 (Box 20, Folder 427)
  - Spring, Leverett, 1888 (Box 20, Folder 428)
  - Springer, Gertrude (Mrs. Louis A.), 1910 (Box 20, Folder 428)
  - Spurgeon, Caroline, 1908 (Box 20, Folder 428)
  - Stanchfield, Clara S. (Mrs. John B.), 1909-1913 (Box 20, Folder 428)
  - Stanchfield, John B., 1900-1907 (Box 20, Folder 428)
  - Stanfield, S. W., 1914 (Box 20, Folder 428)
  - Stanwood, Edward, 1907 (Box 20, Folder 429)
  - Stark, A. B., 1876-1880 (Box 20, Folder 429)
  - Stason, E. J., 1884 (Box 20, Folder 429)
  - Statham, H. Heathcote, 1912 (Box 20, Folder 429)
  - Stechert & Wolff(*), 1873-1895 (Box 20, Folder 430)
  - Stedman, Arthur, 1884 (Box 20, Folder 431)
  - Stedman, Edmund Clarence(*), 1875-1903 (Box 20, Folder 431)
  - Stedman, Laura, 1909 (Box 20, Folder 432)
  - Stempel, Guido Hermann, 1908 (Box 20, Folder 432)
  - Sterling, Clarence, 1876 (Box 20, Folder 432)
  - Stevens, Benjamin Franklin(*), 1873-1894 (Box 20, Folder 433)
  - Stevens, Clara F., 1906 (Box 20, Folder 433)
  - Stevens, David Harrison, 1913 (Box 20, Folder 433)
  - Stevens, Fitz H., 1909 (Box 20, Folder 433)
  - Stevens, Frank B., 1890 (Box 20, Folder 434)
  - Stevens, Frank Jerome, 1902 (Box 20, Folder 434)
  - Stevens, William Oliver, 1905 (Box 20, Folder 434)
  - Stewart, K., 1887-1891 (Box 20, Folder 434)
  - Stewart, L., 1890-1891 (Box 20, Folder 434)
  - Stickney, Mary, 1904 (Box 20, Folder 435)
  - Stiles, Robert, 1896-1905 (Box 20, Folder 435)
  - Stiles, William A.(*), 1874-1895 (Box 20, Folder 435)
  - Stillman, Philip T., 1893 (Box 20, Folder 436)
  - Stock, Charles M., 1910 (Box 20, Folder 436)
  - Stockell, George W., 1877 (Box 20, Folder 436)
  - Stocking, Jay T., 1898 (Box 20, Folder 436)
  - Stoddard, Elliott J., 1913 (Box 20, Folder 436)
  - Stoddard, F. W., 1908 (Box 20, Folder 436)
  - Stoddard, Francis H.(*), 1892-1893 (Box 21, Folder 437)
  - Stoddard, Mary deForest B., 1893 (Box 21, Folder 437)
  - Stoddard, Ralph Waldo, 1904 (Box 21, Folder 437)
  - Stoddart, Harry Taylor, 1898 (Box 21, Folder 437)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps(*), 1895-1915 (Box 21, Folder 438)
  - Stone, Charles Emerson, 1889-1894 (Box 21, Folder 438)
  - Stone, E. Irving, 1909 (Box 21, Folder 439)
  - Stone, William L., 1895 (Box 21, Folder 439)
  - Story, Charles A., 1883 (Box 21, Folder 439)
  - Stoughton, Elizabeth C., [1882?] (Box 21, Folder 439)
  - Strang, Bert D., 1910 (Box 21, Folder 440)
  - Strange, Daniel, 1906 (Box 21, Folder 440)
  - Street, George E., 1883 (Box 21, Folder 440)
  - Strong, Frank, 1904 (Box 21, Folder 440)
  - Strong, Theron G., 1886 (Box 21, Folder 440)
  - Stuart, Donald Clive, 1911 (Box 21, Folder 440)
  - Stuart, Henry, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 440)
  - Sturdy, Joseph, 1898 (Box 21, Folder 441)
  - Sturtevant, Nelly, 1872 (Box 21, Folder 441)
  - Sullivan, B. M., 1892 (Box 21, Folder 441)
  - Sullivan, Catherine, 1899 (Box 21, Folder 441)
  - Sumner, William Graham, 1887, undated (Box 21, Folder 441)
  - Sunday School Times
    See: Patterson DuBois, box 5, folder 122
  - Swain, John Dewell, 1906 (Box 21, Folder 441)
  - Swarthout, B., 1890 (Box 21, Folder 441)
  - Swinburne, Louis J., 1885-1889 (Box 21, Folder 442)
  - Swinnerton, Henry N., 1908 (Box 21, Folder 442)
  - Sydenstricker, Mrs. H. M., 1910 (Box 21, Folder 442)
  - Syle, Louis DuPont, 1893-1894 (Box 21, Folder 442)
  - T-Y - General (Box 21, Folder 443)
  - Taft, William Howard(*), 1908-1914 (Box 21, Folder 444)
  - Tanimura, Issa, 1892 (Box 21, Folder 444)
  - Tappan, William, 1899 (Box 21, Folder 444)
  - Tatman, W. C., 1895 (Box 21, Folder 444)
  - Taylor, Alfred Judd, 1872-1893 (Box 21, Folder 445)
  - Taylor, C. E., 1914 (Box 21, Folder 445)
  - Taylor, Charles Fayette, 1877 (Box 21, Folder 445)
  - Taylor, Henry Osborn, 1913 (Box 21, Folder 445)
  - Taylor, Mary, 1909 (Box 21, Folder 445)
  - Telleen, John Martin, 1904 (Box 21, Folder 446)
  - Tench, Fred, 1890 (Box 21, Folder 446)
  - Tenney, Edward P., 1879 (Box 21, Folder 446)
  - Tesla, Nicola, 1896 (Box 21, Folder 446)
  - Thacher, John Boyd, 1892 (Box 21, Folder 446)
  - Thacher, Thomas Anthony, 1859-1883 (Box 21, Folder 447)
  - Thayer, Joseph Henry, 1896 (Box 21, Folder 447)
  - Thayer, William Roscoe, 1893 (Box 21, Folder 447)
  - Thom, William Taylor, 1881-1888 (Box 21, Folder 447)
  - Thomas, Augustus, 1902-1909 (Box 21, Folder 448)
  - Thomas, Calvin, 1913 (Box 21, Folder 448)
  - Thomas, Isaac, 1881-1910 (Box 21, Folder 448)
  - Thomas, Joseph, 1873 (Box 21, Folder 448)
  - Thompson, Arthur G., 1908 (Box 21, Folder 449)
  - Thompson, Elbert N. S., 1902 (Box 21, Folder 449)
  - Thompson, Frank Lincoln, 1896 (Box 21, Folder 449)
  - Thompson, James K., 1896 (Box 21, Folder 449)
  - Thompson, Robert Ellis, 1881-1882 (Box 21, Folder 449)
  - Thompson, Robert Means, 1896 (Box 21, Folder 449)
  - Thomson, John Stuart, 1913 (Box 21, Folder 450)
  - Thorn, Donaldson Rose, 1906 (Box 21, Folder 450)
  - Thornton, Joseph, 1911 (Box 21, Folder 450)
  - Thrall, J. Brainerd, 1885 (Box 21, Folder 450)
  - Thurber, Samuel, 1908 (Box 21, Folder 450)
  - Thurston, William Porter, 1903 (Box 21, Folder 451)
  - Thwing, Charles Franklin(*), 1892-1894 (Box 21, Folder 451)
  - Tibbals, Charles A., 1892-1894 (Box 21, Folder 452)
  - Ticknor, Benjamin Holt, 1881 (Box 21, Folder 452)
  - Tighe, Ambrose, 1883 (Box 21, Folder 452)
  - Tilley, Morris Palmer, 1909 (Box 21, Folder 452)
  - Tillinghast, William Hopkins, 1895 (Box 21, Folder 452)
  - Todd, Ada Josephine, 1886 (Box 21, Folder 452)
  - Todd, Charles Burr, 1893 (Box 21, Folder 452)
  - Tolman, Albert Harris, 1895 (Box 21, Folder 453)
  - Tomlinson, Joseph, Jr., 1885 (Box 21, Folder 453)
  - Tompkins, Bessie Maclean, 1910 (Box 21, Folder 453)
  - Totten, C. A. L., 1890-1891 (Box 21, Folder 453)
  - Tourtellot, Louis A., 1882-1885 (Box 21, Folder 454)
  - Townsend, George H., 1911 (Box 21, Folder 454)
  - Townsend, Mrs. M. E., 1914 (Box 21, Folder 454)
  - Townsend, Mary L., 1895 (Box 21, Folder 454)
  - Townsend, W. A., 1914 (Box 21, Folder 455)
  - Townsend, William K., 1895 (Box 21, Folder 455)
  - Tracy, Frank B., 1909 (Box 21, Folder 455)
  - Traynor, Patrick, 1892 (Box 21, Folder 456)
  - Treadwell, George Curtis, 1904 (Box 21, Folder 456)
  - Treadwell, Louis S., 1896 (Box 21, Folder 456)
  - Tremper, Florence Nightingale, undated (Box 21, Folder 456)
  - Trent, William P., 1899-1912 (Box 21, Folder 457)
  - Tripler, Charles, 1899 (Box 21, Folder 457)
  - Troup, Phillip, 1910 (Box 21, Folder 457)
  - Trowbridge, Rutherford, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 457)
  - Truey, R. F., 1869 (Box 21, Folder 458)
  - Trumbull, Annie Eliot, 1894 (Box 21, Folder 458)
  - Trumbull, Henry Clay, 1879 (Box 21, Folder 458)
  - Trumbull, James Hammond, 1876-1892 (Box 21, Folder 458)
  - Trumbull, William, 1888 (Box 21, Folder 458)
  - Tucker, Emma Curtiss, 1912 (Box 21, Folder 459)
  - Tucker, Gilbert, 1901 (Box 21, Folder 459)
  - Tucker, Rhoda Mason, 1883-1897 (Box 21, Folder 459)
  - Tuckerman, Bayard, 1885 (Box 21, Folder 459)
  - Tullis, R. L., 1904 (Box 21, Folder 459)
  - Tupper, Frederick, Jr., 1905-1906 (Box 21, Folder 459)
  - Turnbull, G. B., 1895 (Box 21, Folder 460)
  - Turner, Edith, 1908 (Box 21, Folder 460)
  - Turner, Lewis McKenzie, 1909 (Box 21, Folder 460)
  - Tuttle, W. P., 1902 (Box 21, Folder 460)
  - Twentieth Century
    See: Charles Wells Moulton, box 15, folder 328
  - Twichell, Harmony, 1902 (Box 21, Folder 460)
  - Twichell, Joseph(*), 1873-1913, undated (Box 22, Folder 461-463)
  - Twichell, Julia C., 1892 (Box 22, Folder 464)
  - Twichell, Susan L., 1902-1913 (Box 22, Folder 464)
  - Twining, Edward H., 1873 (Box 22, Folder 464)
  - Twining, Julia, 1871 (Box 22, Folder 464)
  - Tyler, Harry W., 1897 (Box 22, Folder 464)
  - Tyler, James Brainerd, 1871 (Box 22, Folder 464)
  - Tyler, Morris Frank, 1876-1886 (Box 22, Folder 465)
  - Tyler, Moses Coit, 1878-1881 (Box 22, Folder 465)
  - Ullman, Jacob, 1900 (Box 22, Folder 465)
  - Unwin, T. Fisher, 1912 (Box 22, Folder 465)
  - Updike, Daniel Berkeley, 1884 (Box 22, Folder 465)
  - Vail, Charles D.(*), 1872-1915 (Box 22, Folder 466-470)
  - Vail, Mrs. Charles D., 1912-1913 (Box 23, Folder 471)
  - Vaile, Edwin O., 1901-1913 (Box 23, Folder 471)
  - Vallette, Francois, 1913 (Box 23, Folder 471)
  - Vanamee, William, 1912 (Box 23, Folder 471)
  - Van Auken, Cora, 1903 (Box 23, Folder 471)
  - Van Benthuysen, C. R., 1885 (Box 23, Folder 471)
  - Van Bergen, R., 1907 (Box 23, Folder 472)
  - Vance, Anne H., 1911-1913 (Box 23, Folder 472)
  - Van Denbeigh, Bertha, 1908 (Box 23, Folder 472)
  - Vanderbilt, William K., 1909 (Box 23, Folder 472)
  - Van Dyke, Henry, 1891-1912 (Box 23, Folder 472)
  - Van Horne, John D., 1911 (Box 23, Folder 473)
  - Van Name, Addison(*), 1873-1905 (Box 23, Folder 473)
  - Vedder, Caroline R., 1906 (Box 23, Folder 474)
  - Vedder, Elihu, 1905-1906 (Box 23, Folder 474)
  - Verrill, Addison E., 1884-1899 (Box 23, Folder 474)
  - Vibbert, William H., 1913 (Box 23, Folder 474)
  - Vickroy, Thomas R., undated (Box 23, Folder 474)
  - Viets, Francis H., 1878 (Box 23, Folder 474)
  - Vincent, Leon Henry, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 474)
  - Wade, William, 1908 (Box 23, Folder 475)
  - Waggener, Leslie, 1888 (Box 23, Folder 475)
  - Wait, Lucien Augustus, 1883 (Box 23, Folder 475)
  - Waite, Alice Vinton(*), 1893-1909 (Box 23, Folder 475)
  - Waite, Henry Randall, 1885 (Box 23, Folder 476)
  - Waith, William, 1903 (Box 23, Folder 476)
  - Walcott, Morgan, 1888 (Box 23, Folder 476)
  - Waldo, Frank, 1905 (Box 23, Folder 476)
  - Walker, Alfred E., 1877 (Box 23, Folder 476)
  - Walker, Alice A.(*), 1884-1887 (Box 23, Folder 477)
  - Walker, E. D., 1889 (Box 23, Folder 478)
  - Walker, Exene, undated (Box 23, Folder 478)
  - Walker, Frances A.(*), 1886-1911 (Box 23, Folder 479)
  - Walker, Francis Amasa(*), 1874-1894 (Box 23, Folder 480)
  - Walker, Grace, 1884-1886 (Box 23, Folder 481)
  - Walker, Katherine K., 1885-1899 (Box 23, Folder 481)
  - Walker, Louise, 1886-1888 (Box 23, Folder 481)
  - Walker, Sophie M.(*), 1884-1913 (Box 23, Folder 482)
  - Wallace, Charles William, 1909 (Box 23, Folder 483)
  - Wallace, Edward, 1895 (Box 23, Folder 483)
  - Waller, Alfred Rayney, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 483)
  - Waller, Thomas McDonald, 1885 (Box 23, Folder 483)
  - Walsh, James J., 1913-1914 (Box 23, Folder 483)
  - Walsh, William S., 1878 (Box 23, Folder 483)
  - Ward, Humphrey, 1892 (Box 23, Folder 484)
  - Ward, Mrs. L. F., 1908 (Box 23, Folder 484)
  - Ward, William Hayes, 1877-1896 (Box 23, Folder 484)
  - Wardlaw, Patterson, 1910 (Box 23, Folder 484)
  - Wardwell, Daniel W., 1873 (Box 23, Folder 484)
  - Ware, William R., 1911 (Box 23, Folder 484)
  - Warfield, Ethelbert D., 1895-1911 (Box 23, Folder 485)
  - Waring, J. Van Vechten, 1894 (Box 23, Folder 485)
  - Waring, Tracy D., 1907-1908 (Box 23, Folder 485)
  - Waring, W. F., 1891 (Box 23, Folder 485)
  - Warner, Charles Dudley(*), 1878-1900 (Box 23, Folder 486-490)
  - Warner, Edwin G., 1902 (Box 24, Folder 491)
  - Warner, George H.(*), 1896-1906 (Box 24, Folder 491)
  - Warner, J. R.(*), 1873-1884 (Box 24, Folder 492)
  - Warner, Louise B. (Mrs. J. R.)(*), 1884-1915 (Box 24, Folder 492)
  - Warner, Susan L. (Mrs. Charles Dudley), 1884-1904 (Box 24, Folder 493)
    See: Mary Barton, box 1, folder 27
  - Warren, Minton, 1874 (Box 24, Folder 493)
  - Warren, William J., 1877 (Box 24, Folder 493)
  - Watrous, Eliot, 1909 (Box 24, Folder 494)
  - Watrous, George D., 1891-1907 (Box 24, Folder 494)
  - Watrous, Lily M., 1893-1894 (Box 24, Folder 494)
  - Watson, Charles A., 1876 (Box 24, Folder 494)
  - Watson, Ellen O., 1898 (Box 24, Folder 494)
  - Watson, Henry M., 1899 (Box 24, Folder 494)
  - Watts-Dunton, Theodore, 1902 (Box 24, Folder 494)
  - Way, W. C., 1878 (Box 24, Folder 495)
  - Wayland, Francis, 1877-1898 (Box 24, Folder 495)
  - Webb, George T., 1911 (Box 24, Folder 495)
  - Webb, Walton, 1906 (Box 24, Folder 495)
  - Weber, William Landor, 1892 (Box 24, Folder 495)
  - Webster, Jean, 1915 (Box 24, Folder 495)
  - Weeks, J. H., 1911 (Box 24, Folder 496)
  - Weeks, John Elmer, 1915 (Box 24, Folder 496)
  - Weir, John Eerguson, 1893-1912 (Box 24, Folder 496)
  - Welch, Lewis Sheldon, 1896-1903 (Box 24, Folder 496)
  - Welch, William H., 1911 (Box 24, Folder 496)
  - Weld, A. G., undated (Box 24, Folder 497)
  - Wells, Daniel H., 1892 (Box 24, Folder 497)